BGM
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good ka
wh was also
ni
me
car
I go every day and night and look at you
I need you
Don't talk to other stars
Believe in me, love, I know you
Write me a note between the flickering lights
Promise me your true love
To be next to me forever
To be able to perform together in our space with all these people
I think we are really lucky to be able to perform together with all these people in our space.
From now on, everyone
Everyone
Let's continue to enjoy being idols!
Let's have fun!
Let's have fun
So please continue to enjoy your time with us
Please continue to enjoy your time with us a lot!
Super step up! Dunk for life!
The good times just keep on coming!
I'll be swinging back from here on out
Beware of blinking!
That's the shoe cloth!
Step up! Dunk for life!
I wanna live a trifecta life that no one's ever lived before Don't worry, I won't get carried away
Follow me, follow me, follow me, follow me till I get the iron pen
I want to live up to your high expectations I want to make you more enthusiastic
More than last year, more than yesterday, more than yesterday, more than yesterday, more than yesterday, more than yesterday, more than yesterday, more than yesterday
That day I was there, hey, wipe your tears
I'm not alone, everyone's here
So let's run to the shining future
Step up, let's go! My dreams are waiting for me
I'm so excited, my feelings are growing faster I'm so excited. I can't stop thinking about you.
Don't give up! Look, the miracle before your eyes
This love that's overflowing Forever Ever
At last, come and feed me every day
Sweetheart, a small toilet
It's all about the ability to change, isn't it?
I'm in the car, I'm in the car, I'm in the car, I'm in the car, I'm in the car, I'm in the car, I'm in the car.
Countless memories, wonderful memories
Mouth watering, so happy
Stay, I want to spread it out and make it sparkle
I want to spread it out and make it sparkle and break out!
I'm serious. Let's get real.
With no false principles
Worries come one after another
But you know what? You can cry. You're not afraid.
The smile system is growing.
It's growing so fast, it's overtaking the times.
See, here's the best part.
Cantrell!
I don't know how long I've been here... but it's been so long...
I want to shout this feeling
Idols are so much fun
I can't get enough of it!
The pulling at the mouth is somehow super fun
When there's a need, everything starts When you're in a hurry, that's when you push
I'll take a break, I'll let you go I'll go again, I'll go again, I'll go again, I'll go again
Clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands.
Clap your hands, clap your hands, clap your hands, monopoly winner, raise your hands
Anxiety is more like a dream than a dream, but there's no such thing as a hot stretch
Now is by far the best time, I'll give you just a little too much
Ima ima ima eri
The next view, and more beyond that, too
Let's go, our dreams are waiting for us
I'm so excited, my heart's pounding I can't stop thinking about it
Don't give up!
Don't give up! Look! The miracle before your eyes is overflowing This love is Forever Ever
Step up! It's show time!
The fun week goes on... Lots and lots of love The weeks will continue to be fun. Lots of love and affection.
A bond that's grown stronger
The best of the best Thank you
If I could communicate with you telepathically
I wish I could telepathically tell you how I feel
You call me when you're lonely
Or tell me when I'm lonely
Or give me a tender hug
Ah, suddenly you look like you're about to say something
Sighing in a puddle
You won't even look me in the eye
I know what's going on in your mind
I want you to squeeze me now
I want you to squeeze me, squeeze me, squeeze me, squeeze me
Catch me so I don't run away so fast
Can I give you a hug?
Squeeze, squish, squish, squish, squish, squish, squish, squish
Squeeze, squish, squish, squish, squish, squish, squish!
I'm getting impatient.
Tell me clearly how you feel.
Hold me close to your chest.
Squeeze me.
I'm getting closer and closer to the station... on my way home.
I can't go on like this. I'm sure I'll have to make a move.
What do you think of me?
I'm ready. All you have to do is be honest with me.
I've been waiting a long time for you to make love.
I've been waiting for the moment when we're ready to make love.
The moment you cleared the air, there was no one else in the world but us.
I'm so shy, I'm so happy, we make eyes at each other and laugh.
I was so in love with you, and I knew that you were the only one for me.
My heart is so tight, so tight, so tight, so tight, so tight, so tight, so tight, so tight, so tight
I have a favor to ask you
Hey, make my heart squeal.
I want you to make me squeal, squeal, squeal, squeal, squeal, squeal, squeal, squeal, squeal, squeal, squeal
Quick, don't ever let go of me. Promise me you won't let go.
I want you to stop the time while I'm still squeaky squeaky squeaky squeaky squeaky squeaky squeaky
I've always felt your warmth more than anyone else I've always felt your warmth more than anyone else.
I feel like I'm going to melt away, love is always so special
I feel like I'm going to melt
Prologue to the many people who have fallen in love with me...
Cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu-cu
More
Squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak
Dozens, tens, tens of thousands of phone calls
More.
Squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak again.
Squeak, squeak, squeak, squeak.
Anna.
A little more.
Just a little more.
I think I'll just stay like this.
Next Episode
Oh, no, skiing!
Skirrus!
Se-no, Bagman Prince!
Oh, no, it's a love bus!
Oh, no, I see it!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. It's okay.
Oh my God, this is so much fun!
I want you to put a fire in my memory.
You know what?
You're so cute!
I want you to light it for me!
They're so cute!
Oh, man!
Does it bother you?
I'm a little worried.
Oh, guys!
Please.
KANAMI
Jr.
HITOKAN HITOKAN
HARUKA
AKI
HIYARI
CHOKKI
CHIZURU
MUCHAN
SHOKOTAN
Bizking
Super-Tokiimeki Advertising Department
LOCK ON
Let's go for it!
Let's do our best!
Thank you very much!
Let's have fun!
Today is the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department's Tokimeki Spring Sunny Stage 2023!
LOVE! Thank you very much for coming to our show!
I am KANAMI Tsujino, a.k.a. KANAMI of Cho-TokiMeki Blue!
What?
Thank you very much.
Excessive jumping is prohibited.
Yes!
Amazing.
So cute.
No standing up for the kissy kissy crowd.
The show will begin shortly.
Are you ready to have some fun?
Oh, my God, it's gonna be great!
Please give us lots of love!
Let's see what you've got!
Okay, let's think about it.
KANAMI
JULIA
HITOKA
ARUKA ARUKA
HIKARI KIWARI
Cho-TokiMeki Seinen Min
Knock on
Oh, I already did it. That, oh, Doki-buri.
Oh, who's that?
Put it out there.
Got it!
One minute left.
Yes, sir.
Oh no!
I'm gonna cry.
I'm going to be moved.
Oh, no!
Oh, man!
Oh, man! Oh, man!
Thirty seconds.
That was fast, fast, fast.
...! Amazon IN38 would give the show a taste of white ENTA
-me
me
Thank you for watching!
Wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah wah
Next Episode Trailer
Next Trailer
Thank you for watching!
Stand tall
Till you catch the sun
All the way
Ready Up
Motivation Bubbles
I'm gonna win, I'm gonna win, I'm gonna win, I'm gonna win, I'm gonna win
When you're about to fall down
Ready up
Let's Re-Up Let's Re-Up
Blow away your thoughts Thoughts
It's okay to dream, isn't it?
Drowning in black, black, black
Sparkling and shining
Beyond the shining point
Let's open up an exciting world
Fly up I can't stop wishing to make it come true
Fly up to the path I believe in
Hoping now
Free Champion
Full of absolute
A dream so big, so big, so big
It's the world, isn't it?
Fly up I can't stop wishing to make it come true
I'm running out of breath, I'm running out of breath, I'm running out of breath
I gotta keep on running, keep on running, keep on running, keep on running, keep on running, keep on running, keep on running, keep on running
Falling down, falling down, falling down...
Don't be in such a hurry
Untie my hands while I'm lost
Oh my babe in love
Oh my babe, don't give up, don't give up, don't give up, don't give up, don't give up, Oh my babe, let's create sensation
Let's make the excitement go on and on and on and on and on and on
Fly up I can't stop the overflowing feelings
Fly up Believe in me, fly forward, find me a little
Hold me now Take me now
Don't be lost
World, bibibibibibikkurā, ai ga once, right?
Fly up
You, my love, have been in one state, nine provinces.
Suck my blood instead of your future
I can see your blood all over the place.
I've got someone to love.
I've worked so hard to get this far
Fly up, I can't stop wishing
I can't stop, I can't stop, I can't stop
To the road we've been running On the road we've been running on
Hoping now Stepping now Jumping nowHoping now Stepping now Jumping now
Beep, beep, beep, beep Bear, you like your dreams, don't you?
Fly up I can't stop the feelings that overflow
Fly up Believe in me, keep pushing forward
Be my hope in a stepping and jumping ground
You ready? Right? Right?
First thing.
I'll be the first to know.
Wow, wow, wow, wow...
Chariot, Chariot, Curérie.
Chariot, chariot, curérie.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah Wow, wow, wow, wow
Freshly made, delivered, delivered, delivered, delivered, delivered
Can we get your team up there?
Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Today, too, we are cheerful and energetic
We take the time and effort to make it!
Kanadaira's dream topping
His shining eyes are shining brightly!
We are proud of our delivery speed and super taste!
each tied with all their might
with overwhelming AIM
with a bang, bang, bang!
with a chip lay
Och-chun, och-chun!
Let's see the skin
Excel O
I'm trying too hard.
The Bellybutton 21st Century
Surprise Peach Tree
Fluttering
Hot, exhilarating
I'll take care of it.
Let's go!
Buchiga ga Delivery
Safe to startSafe to start.
With your heart
Confusion
Starts off set, for a smile like that
Down like a butterfly, stick like a bee
Dye it up before it's too late
My heart is pounding, my rhythm is psychedelic
Every time the wind hits me, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah Wow Wow Wow Wow
Freshly made, delivered, ah-chi-chi, ah-chi-chi, ah-chi-chi, ah-chi-chi, ah-chi-chi
Hey Yo Yo Yo Yo Yo MC Kanami
I'll kill represent Toxen
Doc's live Bite
Dirty and popped out super exclusive
Good boy next door and direct hit
If you're gonna look the other way, it's a blue and red gun
I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it
Chekeracho Chekeracho Chekeracho
Chekeracho, Chekeracho, Chekeracho
Checkerecho, checkerecho, checkerecho, checkerecho, checkerecho...
Yeah
I want to see you in the future
I want to meet you in the 21st century
Surprise, Momojoki, I'm thrilled
Hot, hot, hot, hot
Let's go, we're the delivery
Come on, break it down, make up your heart
Damage
Dance like a butterfly
Do it like a bee
Dye it like a bee before it's a taproot
My heart is pounding
Rhythm is pugi-wugi
What's the fuss?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Ding dong! Hiyori-n brings you a crush!
Tell me how much you like me. Tell her how much you like her.
Ding-dong! Someone's here to give you love!
Ding-dong!
Let's buy some bunnies!
It's the first day of spring for everyone!
Call me Aki-chan more and more!
Shake hands!
Thank you!
Aki-chan's favorite candy
Give me some love, or else I won't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
If there's a brighter night
I'll be your umbrella, I'll be your light
I'll bring you a smile
Let's go, let's go
Let's get the hell out of here and start rebounding
Let's fly, aim for your heart
Super strong guitar, stink like a bee
Slalindo, fold it up
Cruise Boss Game
Let's go, on the sound Recovery Start
Let's go! Let's go!
For your smile
Dance like a butterfly
Like a bee, Steve
I can fly before I can stand
My heart is pounding
Rhythm is Pugilgi
Sorry for all the trouble
Sorry about that.
Hey, hey, hey!
My heart is pounding
Rhythm is pugilistic
We hope to see you again!
Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah
Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Wow, wow, wow, wow.
You got it. Delivery at 8:00 a.m.
What can I get for you?
No, no, no, no.
I was just wondering if you'd be interested in some bangs with seedlings.
You mean the nose?
It's a study in itself.
I'm a pretty girl.
Don't answer me like I'm a pain in the ass.
You have no idea what I'm talking about.
Sarge, please.
I'm really not excited.
I don't feel like dressing up
It's all about the jacket and what's inside.
All you have to do is tell me you like me
All the time, all the time, all the time.
I hate it when you don't touch my love
I don't like it, I don't like it, I don't like it.
Don't look away, don't look away, don't look away, don't look away
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you looking at?
I won't let you.
Don't be a bad boy. I'll spare you.
Give me some love, or I won't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Sound Hodori 사운드 호돌이
Every time you ask me out on a date, I'm the one who asks you out.
I don't want to see you, my love.
Don't keep making excuses for me on the phone.
Do you really care about me?
I can't do this.
I know you're busy.
I'm busy, too.
Send me more love than you already do.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't unravel this. No, no, no, no, no.
You have to be nicer to me than anyone else.
You have to call me more often. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You have to hold my hand outside.
I need you to finish seeing me on our anniversary.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you for watching.
I like you too much. You like me?
I don't know what's going on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Promise me you'll tell me you love me.
You have to give me love all the time, all the time. No, no, no, no, no.
Please spoil me again.
Don't lie to me. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm the only one you should be looking at.
Where are you looking? I won't forgive you!
I'm in love with you, but it's too much
Give me nothing, or I won't forgive you.
Hey, if you know what to say, answer me.
I don't even know what the weather will be like tomorrow.
If it's sunny today, so be it.
I don't care if you think about what no one else knows
I can't help it, so I'll say goodbye
What's important to me is that it's always by my side
It's always so generously overflowing
Inui mai wo tsujite eji
The night sky, a shooting star twinkles
While drowning on the slope
We laughed and laughed and ran.
Someday, I'll remember your voice
I know, so I love you
I love you so much
I can't keep it in an album
I can't keep it in the album, I can't keep it in the album Special days, let's build it up.
Bicycle parking lots and bus stop benches
The sun goes down without finishing the story
Farewell at the crossroads
I'm a little sad on the way to say goodbye
I tried to smile, not wanting you to know
the lights of the city fade away
I can't hold back the tears
When I look back, I can't help but cry
It's not that I'm sad
I don't want to go back
It's just that I'm too mawkish
The night sky, a shooting star is twinkling
A dream with a one-way ticket
I tried to catch up with you
Someday I'll hear your voice too Memories
I know that's why I love you
I love you
I want to touch you
Every time I turn a page
The door of my heart, because we're connected
Contemonial
Considering
algebra
This guy's a master
It's gonna rain tomorrow.
Hey, what about you?
Just like back then.
Don't worry about it.
It's gonna be fine.
You know what I'm saying?
A shooting star in the night sky
Cloudy skies for a long time
I'm thinking about you in my heart I thought of you... in my heart.
I thought of you
Your hair waving in the night wind
Your sweaty shirt bulged as you climbed the hill
Your sweaty shirt bulged and laughed
Everything about you is still Memories
Will never change in the future
In the alpharm that will never fade away
A poisoned connection that can't be locked away
Forever and ever
Thank you all so much for today.
I was so happy to hear your voices for the first time in a long time.
I hope we can make another page of memories together like this.
In the end, I want all of us here to sing as one!
Please let me hear your voices!
La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la
Please subscribe to our channel!
Great feeling! Send more!
Thank you!
I'm going to make you echo at the end.
La La La La...
itable
I love, love, love, love, love, love, love
I can't stop this feeling
I want to be you
I want to be born with a clean face
I want you to step on me and throw me away
And when we grow up and suddenly meet again...
you know...
Or first impressions
Or the worst first impression.
The point is...
Situations you want to mix up
You're the source of evil.
You're the hero of the situation
I've got a secret...
I wish I could have you all to myself over and over again
Since the day I met youFrom the day I met you
my everyday life turned into a romantic comedy.
I love you, I love you, I love you
I exist because of you
Everything
I'm about to pop
More and more
After you
Aim
Someday
May we be united
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
like that
in the pretense of
I came without warning
Look at me as I unwrap the lined paper
I hope you'll be thrilled
I hope you will
club, please.
When I got into the bag
I felt the deck in my heart
I swear to God, I swear to God, it's fate
Hey, you know what? I'm so excited, I'm in trouble
You're the only person in the world I wanna scream
Oh Oh Oh...
SKIP
I don't know what I have to do to make you fall in love with me
Do I have to change myself more?
I've wondered if I should change myself more
I should just be me and you should be me
Yeah, everyone is the hero
I'll live my life like no one else
Oh, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
All that exists for you to be you
I can't hold it in any longer
May we be together somedayMay we be together someday.
Oh.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
All the many feelings you've given me
I wish that all the many feelings you gave me
May these feelings that I have been seeking for you while you were taking me with you
Like, like, like, like, like...
It's okay!
Beyond the full speed
I'm sure something will turn up
I hope to see you at the corner where I can stand
Likes ologie
I like
What male
Oh Oh Oh Oh
I love you
And on the canvas of my broken heart, you paint shards of the future and guide me through it.
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears, I'm lost, I'm crying, I'm crying, I'm crying
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me The cityscape sparkles after the rain
My heart is like a sunny sky, puddles sounding, playing the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye, to me yesterday, after the rain, the streets are sparkling
My heart is like a rainbow, my heart is like a rainbow, my tears are making me cry, I'm going to wear a rainbow dress
Subtitle: Kyou